IGNACIO CONDE

Software Engineer

Profile

I am a dedicated Software Engineer with 2 years of experience and a diverse skill set.

I daily drive Bazzite Linux and I'm a FOSS enthusiast.

Driven by a desire for excellence, I am committed to continue evolving as a developer.

Contact

Location:

1429, Buenos Aires, Argentina

E-Mail:

ignaciomconde@gmail.com

Phone:

+54 (911) 3384-9746

Website:

www.ignaciomconde.com

Technologies

Linux

C, C++, C#

Godot, Unity

Social Media

in: LinkedIn

Github :

Experience

Game Create Repeat - Software Engineer

September 2021 - March 2022

Gameplay Programming (Unity C#):
 Proficient in implementing and optimizing gameplay mechanics, and player interactions to enhance overall gaming experience. Utilizes coding skills to bring creative visions to life, ensuring engaging and immersive gameplay dynamics.

Xappia - Software Developer

June 2019 - August 2020

- Salesforce Programming: Skilled in Apex and Visualforce development, creating tailored solutions to meet diverse business needs on the Salesforce platform.
- Teamwork: Collaborative team player with strong communication skills, fostering synergy and achieving collective goals through open dialogue and shared accountability.

Education

Universidad de Ciencias Empresariales y Sociales - Systems Engineering

2017 - 2018

Computer architecture, Operating systems, Software requirements, Software design, Software construction, Software testing, Databases, Networks and communication protocols.

Languages: C, C++, Java.

Escuela DaVinci - Game Development

2014 - 2015

Game development with Unity (C#), Game design, Graphic design, 3D modeling, Audio recording and editing.